Contact

knick92189@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/kara-de-souza-029259127 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Nursing Critical Thinking Education

Certifications

Acute/Critical Care Nurse - Adult, Pediatric, Neonatal (CCRN)

Adult-Gerontology Acute Care Nurse Practitioner (AGACNP-BC)

Kara de Souza

DNP, APRN, AGACNP-BC, CCRN | Clinical Specialist (Rapid Response & Resuscitation) Soon-to-be Critical Care NP Rockdale

Summary

Kara is a Nurse Practitioner with 8 years of RN experience in critical care and nursing leadership. As a recent graduate from Emory University with her Doctorate in Nursing Practice in Health Systems Leadership & AGACNP, Kara aims to transform healthcare through quality improvement initiatives related to Rapid Response Teams (RRT), resuscitation, and critical care in addition to providing care for patients as a NP at the bedside.

Experience

Northside Hospital 4 years 11 months

Clinical Coordinator August 2017 - Present (2 years 10 months) Atlanta, Georgia

Critical Care

Critical Care Clinician/Educator
July 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 2 months)
Greater Atlanta Area

Northside Hospital Critical Care Registered Nurse July 2012 - July 2014 (2 years 1 month) Greater Atlanta Area

Staff RN

Education

Nell Hodgson Woodruff School of Nursing at Emory University Doctorate of Nursing Practice (Student), Nurse Practitioner, Nursing · (2017 - 2019)

Nell Hodgson Woodruff School of Nursing at Emory University BSN, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (2010 - 2012)